specialtyansweringservice.net 2012-06-23

# Specialty Answering Service Privacy Policy | Specialty Answering Service™

Home > Privacy Policy

## Specialty Answering Service's Privacy Policy

Specialty Answering Service respects your privacy. Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Specialty TAS.

### Information Specialty Answering Service Gathers and Tracks

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the customer's domain name and isp (when possible).

### Use of Information

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, and to possibly customize the content and/or layout of our pages for each individual visitor if applicable. It could also be used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, or to contact consumers for marketing purposes.

### Delete / Deactivate Policy

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please email our main office at info@specialtyansweringservice.net, or using the mailing address below.

### Notification of Changes

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

### Security Policy

Specialty Answering Service takes every reasonable precaution to protect our user's information. When you submit information, your information is protected both on-line and off-line in accordance with applicable laws, regulations, and industry standards. For example, with out limitation, Specialty Answering Service uses a full-time Network Administrator, ssl servers, pgp, and 128-bit data encryption to protect the confidentiality of the information you provide.

We can be reached via e-mail at info@specialtyansweringservice.net, by phone at 1-888-532-4794, or by mail at

**Specialty Answering Service  
198 Allendale Road, Suite 305  
King of Prussia, PA 19406**

Specialty Answering Service takes online privacy seriously, and does not share the information users have submitted without their permission.
